test-bank.com 2015-04-08

# Privacy Policy - TEST-BANK.COM : TEST-BANK.COM

**Placing Orders**

All the orders (payments) will be processed by Clickbank, the internet leading retailer of digital products. [Clickbank’s Privacy Policies](https://accounts.clickbank.com/privacy.html).  
Clickbank provides us with the necessary information to process our clients’ orders including the name, email address and the order details. We do not have access to any credit cards information.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, when placing an order, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**How we use collected information**

Test-Bank may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

* To improve customer service  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently. 
* To improve our Site  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services. 
* To process payments  
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service. 
* To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them. 
* To send periodic emails  
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. 

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Test-Bank has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at  
request@test-bank.com

This document was last updated on August 12, 2013

Privacy policy created by Generate Privacy Policy
